<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resumes on Matt Gibson</title>
    <link>/resume/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resumes on Matt Gibson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/resume/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>/resume/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/education/</guid>
      <description> Education I am currently attending the University of Texas at Austin, where I will earn a Bachelor of Science and Arts degree in Biology with certificates in Pre-health and Forensic Science. I am on track to graduate in May 2020.
 Skills I have strong personal and leadership skills. I also have a basic skills in R-Studio.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/resume/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Matt Gibson! I am currently a senior at the University of Texas at Austin studying biology. I was born and raised as a Longhorn here in Austin so attending UT had always been a dream of mine! I enjoy sports, both watching and playing, traveling and spending time with friends and family. I also have a two year old Golden Retriever named Nala! Here’s a picture of her eating whats left of a cupcake on her birthday:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Service</title>
      <link>/resume/community-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/community-service/</guid>
      <description>Riverbend Church -Volunteered as youth leader at Vacation Bible School
 Westlake Hills Presbyterian Church -Volunteered for church mission trip to New Orleans - provided companionship and quality of life assistance to the elderly and individuals with special needs
 Austin 10/20 Race -Volunteered for race support crew prior to and day of event
 Youth Basketball Coach -Coached recreational youth basketball for the Westlake Youth Basketball Association (WYBA)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Experience</title>
      <link>/resume/work-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/work-experience/</guid>
      <description> Lost Creek Country Club -Lifeguard
-Summer 2015-present
 The County Line BBQ -Waiter
-Summer 2018
 Independent -Mass Marketing mailer preparation
-Summer 2016, 2017
 Intership -Interned at Neal Dental Group in Austin, Texas
-Fall 2017
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>