<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matt Gibson</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Matt Gibson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Here is some python stuff we learned!</title>
      <link>/blog/here-is-some-python-stuff-we-learned/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/here-is-some-python-stuff-we-learned/</guid>
      <description> library(reticulate) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>url: Project 1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/projects/prject-1_eda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/prject-1_eda/</guid>
      <description>With the recent federal legalization of sports gambling I believe that sports data will become increasingly important and relevant in successfully predicting outcomes of games. For this project I obtained NFL gambling and game data from kaggle.com. The first data set included data on individual games such as schedule year and date, stadium name, home team score, away team score, and spread. The second data set recorded weather related data for these same NFL games, which included temperature, precipitation, location, stadium type (open-air or dome) and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/projects/project222/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project222/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Heart disease is the leading cause of death in the U.S. Knowing this, I wanted to determine if heart disease could be pridcted based on a certain group of indicators. In an attempt to find an answer, I obtained a data set of patients from kaggle.com in order to build a model to predict heart disease based on a patients’ symptoms when first admitted to the hospital. The dataset has 15 variables and 303 observations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>