<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matt Gibson</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Matt Gibson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>/resume/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/education/</guid>
      <description> Education I am currently attending the University of Texas at Austin, where I will earn a Bachelor of Science and Arts degree in Biology with certificates in Pre-health and Forensic Science. I am on track to graduate in May 2020.
 Skills I have strong personal and leadership skills. I also have a basic skills in R-Studio and python.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/resume/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Matt Gibson! I am currently a senior at the University of Texas at Austin studying biology. I was born and raised as a Longhorn here in Austin so attending UT had always been a dream of mine! I enjoy the outdoors, sports - both watching and playing, traveling and spending time with friends and family. I also have a two year old Golden Retriever named Nala!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Service</title>
      <link>/resume/community-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/community-service/</guid>
      <description>Riverbend Church -Volunteered as youth leader at Vacation Bible School
 Westlake Hills Presbyterian Church -Volunteered for church mission trip to New Orleans - provided companionship and quality of life assistance to the elderly and individuals with special needs
 Austin 10/20 Race -Volunteered for race support crew prior to and day of event
 Youth Basketball Coach -Coached recreational youth basketball for the Westlake Youth Basketball Association (WYBA)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here is some python stuff we learned!</title>
      <link>/blog/here-is-some-python-stuff-we-learned/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/here-is-some-python-stuff-we-learned/</guid>
      <description>Regular Expressions! Towards the end of the semester, we learned about regular expressions, commonly refered to as regex. We can use regex to find patterns in strings using algorithms and functions such as re.findall. Regex can be applied in a biological context in many way. Below I will demontrate just one of these ways.
 Restriction Enzyme Example Here is an example from one of our homeworks. Here, I used re.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Experience</title>
      <link>/resume/work-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/work-experience/</guid>
      <description> Lost Creek Country Club -Lifeguard
-Summer 2015-present
 The County Line BBQ -Waiter
-Summer 2018
 Independent -Mass Marketing mailer preparation
-Summer 2016, 2017
 Intership -Interned at Neal Dental Group in Austin, Texas
-Fall 2017
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/projects/prject-1_eda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/prject-1_eda/</guid>
      <description>With the recent federal legalization of sports gambling I believe that sports data will become increasingly important and relevant in successfully predicting outcomes of games. For this project I obtained NFL gambling and game data from kaggle.com. The first data set included data on individual games such as schedule year and date, stadium name, home team score, away team score, and spread. The second data set recorded weather related data for these same NFL games, which included temperature, precipitation, location, stadium type (open-air or dome) and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/projects/project222/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project222/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Heart disease is the leading cause of death in the U.S. Knowing this, I wanted to determine if heart disease could be pridcted based on a certain group of indicators. In an attempt to find an answer, I obtained a data set of patients from kaggle.com in order to build a model to predict heart disease based on a patients’ symptoms when first admitted to the hospital. The dataset has 15 variables and 303 observations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>